Guide to the Kenneth M. Cuthbertson Papers SC0582
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2000-021
  - ROTC (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Residence Operating Committee (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - "S" old (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Sacramento Dinner June 25, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Sherman, Thomas H. (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - SIDEC--Stanford International Development Center (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - SLAC--Coordinating Committee (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Emmett Solomon (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Speech Association (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Student-Faculty Staff Meetings (Pat Shea et al.) (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Associates--Board of Governors (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Union (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Student Aid Committee (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Student Development Committee: Special Projects and Fund Raising (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Cowell Student Health Center (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Trailers (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - University Address Lists (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - University Policy (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - University Presidents' Meetings (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - University Research Association (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Vice President for Finance--Office of (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Computer Sciences New Building (531) (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Computing and Software (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - Consolidated Mortgage Company (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Construction Projects--Completed (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - John C. Cosgrove (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Financial Needs (Cosgrove Correspondence) (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Cost of Education Funds (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Counseling and Testing Center (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Counterpart (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - D (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Del Monte Properties (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Delta Tau Delta (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Development Film Responses (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Finance Director of (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - DoD (University Posture with) (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Doyle, Morris M. (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Drama Repertory Theater (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Driving Range Lights - Golf (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Bill Earl - O.K. Earl Corporation (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Earth Sciences (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Eating Clubs (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Educational Opportunity Bank (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Electrical Northeast Loop Completion (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Encina Commons (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Engineering (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - "F" (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Faculty-Staff (Distinguished Chair, Salaries, Research Cont. and Grant) (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Fellowships (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Financial Information - Budgeting, Long Range Forecasting (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Financing Higher Education (general) (Including Financial Aid at Stanford) Planning and Management Data (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Campuses (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Fraternity House Valuation Committee (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Fund Raising (Includes other colleges and Universities) (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Fund Raising Objectives, Opportunities and Problems (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Funds, Specifically Invested (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - General Fund Formulae (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - General Plant - Miscellaneous (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Gift Prospects - 1970 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Gifts and Bequests to Higher Education ($5,000,000 and over) (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Gifts - Unrestricted - Reinvestment (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - HHFA Government Loans for Housing - MSH, etc. (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Governmental Relations - 1970 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Grants and Contracts - Government Backlog and Expense Levels (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - HEFA (general) (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - HEFA Title I, II, III (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - HEPL Project (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Hoover Institution (and Hoover Awards) (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins Marine Station - KMC (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - HUD loans and room and Board rates (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - SLAC Coordinating Committee (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Space Facilities Program (See also Space Planning Coordinating Committee) (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Space Planning Coordinating Committee (Facilities Committee) (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Alumni Association (General) (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Faculty Club (old) (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Judicial Council (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Stanford-in-Washington (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - SRI October 1968-May 1969 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Stewart, Arthur C. (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Storke Student Publications Building (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Street Signs-Lightning (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Student Affairs (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Student Affairs (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Student Budget Committee (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Student Center for Innovation in Research and Education (SCIRE) (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Student Disciplinary Cases Considered by SJS and Dean of Students (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Student Committee for Involvement in Politics (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Student Financial Aid (up thru 1967) Federal and State Loans Parent Letter (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Student Hospitalization Committee (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Student Residences General (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Summer English and Academic Orientation (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Summer Festival (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Symonds, Nathaniel M. (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - T (old) (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Transportation Stanford-Berkley (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Traveling Professors (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Tresidder Memorial and Cultural Arts Division (Stanford Union) Century 21 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Tuition 1967 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Tuition (and Fees) thru 1966 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - U (old) (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Library (1967) (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - United Fund (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - University Council (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Utilities Master Plan (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - V (old) (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Venture Capital Company (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Vice President for Business Affairs (Alf Brandin) (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Visiting Committees (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - W (old) (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Women's Clubhouse (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - X-Y-Z (old) (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Academic Statesman (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Achilles, Theodore C. (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - American Express Investment Management Company (formerly Fund American) (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Annual Fund (old) (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Applications for Employment (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Applied Physics (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Advisory CTEE, Proposed Building Program (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Art Building Dedication (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Art Department (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Associated Students (ASSU) to 1969 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Department-Buck Club, Maples Pavilion, on Policy, etc. (old) (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - A (old) (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - B (old) (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Bechtel International Student Center (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - California, University of (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - California School Employees Association (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Chemical Engineering Building (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry Building (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - "C" old (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Childs, Mr. Leroy - Pottery Shack (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Class Agents Programs (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - College Law Bulletin (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Communications Committee (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Corn Projects Development Company; Dr. John D. Garber, Dr. Arnold C. Ott (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - "D" old (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Dornbusch - McAfee Research Project (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Energy Systems, Inc. (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Experimental College (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - "E" old (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - "F" old (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Fire - President's Office Building (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - "G" old (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Gift Prospects - gifts through 1969 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Gift Prospects - gifts old (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Dean Robert J. Glaser (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Louis E. Goodman Memorial (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Governmental Relations, Jan. - July 1969 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Governmental Relations, through 1968 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - "A" 1968 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - ADP - Administrative Data Processing (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Admissions 1968-69 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - AEL staff members - severance pay (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Affiliate programs general (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action Program - AAP (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - AICCU through Aug. 1969 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - AICCU 1969 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Air conditioning (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Allan, Robert M., Jr. (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Altamont (case on Stanford) (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - American Indian Project (Stanford) (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Arden House (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Arts Management, centralized (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Associated Students (ASSU) from 1969 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Dept. (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Dept. - Buck Club Achievement Awards (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Athletics - Roscoe Maples Pavilion (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Athletics - Shrine East-West Game (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - "B" (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Bailey, Roy B. (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Ball, George W. (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Bayshore Employment Service, Inc. (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Bechtel, Stephen D. (both Sr. and Jr.) (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Jayne Berry Fund (Lowell Berry) (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Bing, Peter S. M.D. (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Biology Building (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Black Businesses (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Bowman House - remodeling (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Boyd Ranch (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Brigham Young University (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Brown University (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Building Project Guidelines (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - 1968-69 budget and revisions (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - 1967-68 budget (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Building and plant needs (estimated 1960-70) (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Building 10 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - "C" 1969-70 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - California, University of (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - California, University of - fundraising (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Campus summer alumni colleges and reunions (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Carter Report (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Central Food Service Building (#383C) (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Centrex Telephone System (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Chandler, Otis (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Chemistry - subbasement (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Classified contracts (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - The Closed Corporation - book review (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Coalition for an academic community (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - College costs, accounting systems, and financing strategies - Antioch College (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - College readiness program (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Campus Protest (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Computation CenterCampaign for Stanford Files (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2000-042
  - General Files, Subseries 1
    - Affiliated programs (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 1, Folder 2-5)
    - Affirmative Action - GSO (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - Affirmative Action Meeting 1975-76 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Affirmative Action External (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Affirmative Action - Women (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alpine Chalet (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Assoc. (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
    - Alumni Clubs 1973-75 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Day College 1974-76 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Alumni - Interim Report… 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Building Gifts (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Campus Report (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Committees, General (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Computers (Box 1, Folder 20-23)
    - Daily, Stanford, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Davis, Angela 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Energy Crisis 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Ethnic Proposals 1969-73 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Faculty 1974-77 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Club 1970-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Founder's Day 1973-77 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Fundraising 1971-73 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Gold Spike Award (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Inaugurations (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Legal Services (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Minority Affairs (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
    - Musicales (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Naming of Univ. Bldgs. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Parking (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
    - Pew Trusts (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
    - Paleger, Herman (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Pigott, McCone (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Plant Services (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
    - Pledge Forms (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - President's Emergency Assistance Fund (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Price, Sol (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Princeton Univ. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Privacy of Information 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Private Universities (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Progress Fund (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Publications (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
    - Purity Stores (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Q. Misc. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Quad Proposal (Hist. Preserv. Fund) 1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - R. Misc. (Box 2, Folder 34-37)
    - Raychem (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Raymond, Robert (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Reis, Mrs. William (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Research Guidelines (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Richards, Mabel Wilson Scholarship Fund 1971-76 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Richman, Frederick I. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Family 1971-77 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Foundation 1971-76 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Rose, Billy Foundation (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Rosen, Carl (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Rosenberg, Sydney & Theodore 1971-77 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Rosencranz, Armin D. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Rosenkranz, George (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Roth, Mrs. William P. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Rubin, Miles (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Russell, Madeleine Haas (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Sa, Misc. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Sc-Se, Misc. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Sh, Misc. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Si, Misc. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Sk-Sl (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Sm-So (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Sp-Sq (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Sta-Ste (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Sto-Sua (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Swe-Sz (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Sachs, Mrs. Alexander (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Sacramento Host (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco Foundation (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    - Scaife, Richard (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Scudder, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sears Roebuck Foundation (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Seeley Mudd Fund 1971-77 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Segerstrom, Henry (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Setzer, G. Cal (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Shell Companies Foundation (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Shelton, Talbot (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Sloan, Alfred D. Foundation (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Solar Energy Institute (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Space (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - GSO Ex. Comm. Minutes 1972 Aug. - Dec. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - GSO Ex. Comm. Minutes 1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - GSO Ex Comm Minutes 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - GSO Ex Comm Minutes 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - PACE Files, Subseries 2
    - PACE Bi-Weekly Reports 1961-62 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Campaign Communique 1961 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Plan of Action 1961 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Campaign Organization Handbook 1960 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Publicity and Public Relations Plan 1961 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Case for Stanford (Publ.) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Edge of Greatness (Publ.) 1963 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Plan of Campaign July 1-Dec. 31, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Chairmen's Conference Sept. 21-22, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
    - A Challenge for Stanford, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Evaluation Reports, 1961-64 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Ford FDN - Report of Grant Expend. 1960-64 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Ford FDN - Report, Draft 1963 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Ford FDN - Interim Report, Drafts (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Ford FDN - Interim Report, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Ford FDN - Report April 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Ford FDN - Final Report, Aug. 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Pace Paperweight (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Pace Announcement 1961 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Pace Program - documentation, clippings 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Newsletter, June 1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Leadership Conference 08-27-28, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
  - Campaign for Stanford Files, Subseries 3
    - Campaign for Stanford - Campaign Plans 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Ex. Comm. Minutes 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Ex. Comm. Minutes 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Ex. Comm. Minutes 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Ex. Comm. Minutes 1976-77 (Box 5, Folder 13)